I just want to say this, what you are learning is that your captors, the monsters, those
that go bump in the night, are mortal.
What you are learning is that that which you felt is what you knew.
Do not take all of this as overwhelm.
Take it as undergirding.
Take it as inspiration, because when you know that all the pain and all the deception
and all the harm was caused by people, you know that they are not invincible.
They're not invincible.
And to be quite honest, if they were aliens, they'd have to actually then show that.
I want you to remember there was a time before them, and this is now the time to end it.
I also want you to remember that it doesn't take more than a generation to change the course of things.
This whole idea of, like, we may not be here to see, like, a better future.
Fuck that.
I was going along with that.
Time we've been here, watching all of this go down, and we don't learn enough, and we don't have enough within us to apply.
We're not in the recovery stage.
We're not in the learning curve.
That's what we mean when we say, listen to our ancestors.
Them folks, they're the ones that went through all...
So that it could live in us, so that we could wake it up.
Nah, I'm not.
I'm gonna be here.
Going to be.
To see the shit go down.
I lived all them other lives through it, so that I could be here to see it end.
Thank you.